athlonsports.com 2018-12-29

# 

**Athlon sports**

**Privacy Policy**

_Last Updated_ : May 25, 2018

**1.               **** Overview**

We are Athlon Sports Communications, Inc. (dba AMG Parade), including Parade.com, AthlonSports.com and CommunityTable.com (collectively, “ _Athlon_ ,” “ _we_ ,” “ _us_ ,” or “ _our_ ”).  This “ _Privacy Policy_ ” governs each website, mobile site, application, and any service provided thereby, regardless of how distributed, transmitted, published, or broadcast (each, a “ _Service_ ”) provided by Athlon Sports Communications Inc., its parent, subsidiaries and/or affiliates that links to this Privacy Policy. 

We have developed this Privacy Policy to inform you how we collect data through our Services, how we use the collected data, and a user’s rights with respect to the collected data.  This Privacy Policy is binding on all those who access, visit and/or use our Services, whether acting as an individual or on behalf of an entity, including you and all persons, entities, or digital engines of any kind that harvest, crawl, index, scrape, spider, or mine digital content by an automated or manual process or otherwise (collectively, “ _user_ ,” “ _you_ ,” or “ _your_ ”).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you do not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, then do not access or use any of our Services.  By accessing and/or using a Service, you accept and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use [[https://policies.athlonsports.com/user-agreement](https://policies.athlonsports.com/user-agreement)], which is hereby incorporated by reference.

**2.               ****Information we collect from you and how we collect it**

_Information We Collect_.  We collect information about your use of our Service, including but not limited to: your online behavior, your Internet connections, mobile, or other device computer equipment, as well as the site(s), application(s), destination(s), and/or service(s) visited before using or accessing the Services, and after leaving the Services, along with your time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other similar information about traffic and usage, as you navigate to, through, and away from our website(s), including other clickstream data. This is “ _Non-Personal Data_ ,” which does not directly, personally identify you. 

We also use “ _cookies_ ” to enhance your use of our Services.  A cookie is information either temporarily or permanently stored in a file on your computer.  You can set your browser to reject cookies, but that may limit your use of some convenient features of our Service(s).  For more information on cookies and how our Services use cookies, please see our Cookie Notification [[https://policies.athlonsports.com/cookie-policy](https://policies.athlonsports.com/cookie-policy)].

_Information You Provide, Directly and Indirectly_.  You may register to use our Services, set up an account, enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a survey, make a payment, subscribe to our Services, or respond to communications (e.g., surveys, polls, requests for feedback).  We will collect the information you provide to us.  This may include your IP address, first and last name(s), demographic information, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, credit card number, and any other information you provide to us.  Such information may also include the geographic location of you and/or your computer, mobile or other device, as well as date/time stamp, IP address, your computer (e.g., the make, model, settings, and specifications, including but not limited to your CPU speed, connection speed, browser type, operating system, device identifier).  While using our Services, you may also transmit your communication preferences, your physical location, your demographic information (e.g., your age, marital status, ethnicity/race, and gender), and other information.  All of this is “ _Personal Data_ ,” which can be used to personally identify you. 

Additionally, if you choose to access, visit, and/or use any _third party social networking service(s)_ that may be integrated with our Service, we may receive your Personal Data and other information about you and your computer, mobile, or other device that you have made available to those social networking services, including information about your contacts on those services.  For example, some social networking services allow you to push content from our Service to your contacts or to pull information about your contacts so you can connect with them on or through our Service.  Some social networking services also will facilitate your registration for our Service or enhance or personalize your experience on our Service.  Your decision to use a social networking service in connection with our Service is voluntary.  However, you should make sure you are comfortable with the information your third-party social networking services may make available to our Service by visiting those services’ privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy settings directly with those services.

**3.               ****How we use information about you**

_For Legitimate Interests_.  Athlon uses information collected by clickstream data collection, web pixels, and cookies to store your preferences, improve website navigation, make personalized features and other services available to you, compile and analyze aggregate statistics and trends, and otherwise help administer and improve the Services.  We may identify you from your Personal Data and merge or co-mingle Personal Data and Non-Personal Data, for any lawful business purpose.  Where you provide registration information, cookies can also be used to identify you when you log onto the Services or portions of the Services.  Except as otherwise stated, we may use information we collect from you for the legitimate business purpose of providing our Services to you, including, but not limited to:

·       to administer the Services 

·       to help diagnose problems with our servers 

·       to customize our Services to your preferences

·       to communicate information to you (e.g., new features, products, or services)

·       to check on your account status

·       to improve our Services

·       to work with our service providers who perform certain business functions or services on our behalf and who are bound by contractual obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy

·       to show you content and sponsored messaging based on geographic location information from you and/or your computer, mobile, or other device

·       to prevent or investigate fraud (or for risk management purposes), or to comply with a legal obligations, court order, or in order to exercise our legal claims or to defend against legal claims

·       to conduct aggregate analysis and develop business intelligence that helps us to enhance, operate, protect, make informed decisions and report on the performances of our Services 

·       for other purposes identified to you and as requested by you (please note that you have the right to withdraw your consent to such use at any time by contacting us via the information below)

_With the Consent of a Data Subject within the European Union.   _If we have obtained your consent, we may also use your information:

·       to share your information with our corporate parents, subsidiaries, other affiliated entities, and associated entities for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy

·       to send e-mail and postal mail to provide you with updates and news

·       to process any request you make

·       to process any commercial transaction, including but not limited to fulfilling an order or subscription request

·       to process your Personal Data as described throughout this Policy

·       to process your Non-Personal Data as outlined as described throughout this Policy

_Performance of a Contract_.  If you have agreed to our terms of use, or other terms of service, and you have created an account, purchased merchandise, signed up for a subscription, or entered into a contest or sweepstakes, we may also use your information:

·       to establish your account to use the Services

·       to validate your username, e-mail, password, and/or other login credentials

·       to respond to your requests

·       to provide you with merchandise you have requested

·       to fulfill your subscription purchase(s)

·       to notify you of your contest or sweepstakes results

·       to send you e-mail and postal mail supplying you with the most recent service information or to send you information about your order (e.g., order confirmations, shipment notifications, etc.)

·       to notify you of any changes to relevant agreements or policies

In each case, we may use third‐party e‐mail providers to deliver these communications to you.

**4.               ****Sharing Personal Data with third parties**

We may sell or share information about you and your computer, mobile, or other device, including without limitation, your Personal Data, with our parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think may offer services and/or products that may be of interest to you.  Additionally, we may use, transfer, assign, sell, share, and provide access to your Personal Data and other information about you and your computer, mobile, or other device that we receive through third-party social networking services.  We may use, transfer, sell, and share your and Non-Personal Data, aggregated with other users’ Non-Personal Data, for any lawful business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers, sponsors, clients, and customers.

In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets.  In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by us, our parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Service users may be among the transferred assets.

Athlon may also share Personal Data it collects with any third party or outside mailing list, in the following circumstances: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (e) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Athlon, its users, or the general public; (f) for purposes of health, safety and other matters in the public interest ; (g) by virtue of undergoing any change in control, including in connection with corporate restructuring, sale or assignment of assets, merger, divestiture, and other changes of control or financial status, in which case we will require the recipient to use such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy; (h) to Athlon’s affiliates, successors, and agents/representatives (for example, consultants), which are required to treat the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy; or (i) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure.

**5.               ****Third-Party Service Providers**

We use third-party service providers to help us operate our Services, who may collect, store, and/or process the information detailed herein.  We allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, market research, community and forums management, auction services, and shopping, personal/job search, and other classified ads functionality, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services.

If you choose to purchase merchandise, products, and/or services on or through features on the Service, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card or other payment processing, order fulfillment, credit pre-authorization, and address verification.  There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the Service that may be managed or participated in by third parties. In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third party(ies), each pursuant to its own policies.  We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests.  

Athlon uses commercially reasonable efforts to engage with third parties that post a privacy policy governing their collection, processing, and use of Non-Personal Data and Personal Data.  **While we may seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, and you agree that we  do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.**

_Google Analytics_.  We have enabled Google Analytics to collect data about our traffic through the use of Google advertisements and other anonymous identifiers. We use Google Analytics cookies and other cookies to compile data to better understand users and provide users with a more tailored experience.  You can opt out of Google Analytics by visiting Google’s Opt-Out Browser Add-on website here, [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

_Google AdX_.  We use Google AdX to help with managing many of our revenue sources related to online display advertising inventory and allows us to buy and sell ad space on or relating to our Service(s). You can view Google AdX’s privacy policy at [https://support.google.com/adxbuyer/answer/  
1325008?hl=en](https://support.google.com/adxbuyer/answer/1325008?hl=en). 

_Google AdSense_.  Our Service(s) utilize Google AdSense to promote and manage advertising on those Service(s) tailored to our content and audience. The privacy policy for Google AdSense can be reviewed at [https://termsfeed.com/blog/privacy-policy-google-adsense/](https://termsfeed.com/blog/privacy-policy-google-adsense/). 

_AOL_. We use AOL’s software platform for digital advertising personalization across our Service(s), including brand integration and analysis of advertising trends, to create a positive experience with our Service(s)for desktop, mobile, and tablet users.  AOL Advertising’s privacy policy can be found at [https://privacy.aol.com/legacy/index.html](https://privacy.aol.com/legacy/index.html). 

_Sharethrough_.   Sharethrough’s advertising software is utilized on our Service(s)to manage native ad strategy including sales, delivery, and management.  You can review Sharethrough’s privacy policy at [https://platform-cdn.sharethrough.com/privacy-policy](https://platform-cdn.sharethrough.com/privacy-policy).  

_ZergNet_.  7hops.com, Inc., doing business as ZergNet, is used in contextual advertising, such as ad and article recommendations and sponsored links.  ZergNet’s privacy policy can be found at [https://www.zergnet.com/privacy](https://www.zergnet.com/privacy). 

_AddThis_.  AddThis is a social bookmarking service that can be used for advertising analysis and integrated into a website with the use of a web widget.  You can view AddThis’ privacy policy at [http://www.addthis.com/privacy](http://www.addthis.com/privacy). 

_Quantcast_. Quantcast specializes in AI-driven real-time advertising audience feedback and measurement.  By placing tags on websites, blogs, videos and widgets, the firm measures metrics such as audience age and gender makeup, areas of interest and type, length and frequency of their engagement with certain types of content.  Quantcast’s privacy policy can be reviewed at [https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/). 

_YouTube_.  We use YouTube to deliver video content through our Service(s).  You can learn more about YouTube’s data collection practices through its privacy policy, which is available at [https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/7671399?p=privacy_guidelines&hl=en&visit_id=1-636628128110092664-2082382643&rd=1](https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/7671399?p=privacy_guidelines&hl=en&visit_id=1-636628128110092664-2082382643&rd=1). 

_Facebook_.  We use Facebook’s conversion tracking pixel and retargeting service(s) to monitor users who are redirected to the Service(s)after clicking on a Facebook ad.  This allows us to monitor our ads and their effectiveness, as well as to provide advertisements to users for products according to their interests.  Facebook explains conversion tracking on its website [[https://www.facebook.com/business/a/online-sales/conversion-tracking](https://www.facebook.com/business/a/online-sales/conversion-tracking)], and Facebook explains its use of Cookies and other storage technologies, as well as how to control Facebook’s use of Cookies, on its site here [hyperlink: [https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/)].  You can access Facebook’s privacy policy at [https://www.facebook.com/policy.php](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

_Twitter_.  We use Twitter’s widget to facilitate connection between Your Twitter account the Service(s).  Twitter receives data based on this widget.  For information about Twitter’s Privacy Policy, visit its website [[https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en](https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en)] or learn about Twitter’s “Tailored Suggestions,” here [[https://support.twitter.com/articles/20169421](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20169421)].

_Other Third-Party Services_.  In addition to the applications listed above, we use other third-party services to obtain, track, and store user information.  By way of example, we use a Customer Relations Management (CRM) software to manage customer data and information. We also use a third-party software to collect information from your browser and computer device in order to capture and analyze user behavior on our Service(s).  The software allows us to track and monitor such actions as clicks, taps, and scrolling behavior.  From time to time, we will use additional content or applications on our Service(s) that are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, social media websites, content providers, and application providers.  These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other Internet tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Site.  The information they collect may be associated with your Personal Data or they may collect information, including Personal Data, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services.  We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. You can learn more about opting out of third-party vendors’ use(s) of cookies by visiting the “Network Advertising Initiative” website [[http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)].  You may also visit other websites, such as [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), for more information.

**6.               ****How Personal Data is protected**

Athlon takes reasonable steps online and offline to safeguard the Personal Data that you provide to us, including Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encrypted connections (HTTPS) to the web site(s) on our Service(s), secure multi-tiered firewalls, and portions of your data may also be encrypted on our storage server for additional security. 

Nonetheless, it is common knowledge that transmission of information via the internet is not wholly secure, and we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Data, or any other information, transmitted to or through any of our Service(s).  Any transmission of Personal Data, or other information, is at your own risk.  By using our Service(s), you acknowledge and accept these risks.  As a result, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us or that are otherwise provided to us and we cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of information.   It is your responsibility to safeguard any passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features associated with your use of the Service(s).  Any transmission of information is at your own risk.  By using our Service(s), you acknowledge and accept these risks.

Please notify us immediately at  [help@amgparade.com](mailto:help@amgparade.com) if you become aware of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of Service security or of this Policy.  If our security system is breached, we will notify you of the breach only if and to the extent required under applicable law.

**7.               ****Your choices, access, and rights to your Personal Data**

You may change, edit, update, or delete the information you provided, when you set up your account through our Service(s), through your account settings.  You may also request the deletion of this information by sending an e-mail to [help@amgparade.com](mailto:help@amgparade.com).

In certain jurisdictions, you may also have the following rights and options with regard to accessing, reviewing, correcting, and updating your Personal Data, as well as how we use and disclose your Personal Data:

_Right to Access_.  We respect your right to access and control your information, and we will respond to requests for information and, where applicable, will correct, amend, or delete your Personal Data. 

·       _How to Access Your Personally Identifiable Information._ You may choose to access or update Personal Data, by logging into the account you have created with our Service(s), if applicable.

·       _Access to Personal Data_.  You may choose to access your Personal Data by contacting us and requesting access, a process which shall include our identity verification procedures.  Before providing data to you, we will ask for proof of identity and sufficient information about your interaction with us so that we can locate any relevant data. We may also charge you a fee for providing you with a copy of your data (except where this is not permissible under local law).

_Updating Communications Preferences (Opt-Out) and Unsubscribing.  _You may choose to receive promotional offers, newsletters, and similar communications from us regarding products and services of Athlon and our affiliated organizations.  You may opt out of receiving such communications from us by communicating your preferences to us at [help@amgparade.com](mailto:help@amgparade.com), or in the case of e-mails, by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the applicable e-mail. 

_Right to Rectify — Correction and Deletion_. In some jurisdictions, you have the right to correct or amend your Personal Data if it is inaccurate or requires updating. You may also have the right to request deletion of your Personal Data; however, this is not always possible due to legal requirements and other obligations and factors.  Remember that you can update your account information by contacting us at help@amgparade.com.

_Right to Erasure /  Be Forgotten_.  You may request that we delete your Personal Data in certain circumstances, such as if holding the Personal Data is no longer necessary or if part of your Right to Object (below). **Please note that if you request erasure of your account, Athlon, in complying with your request, shall also delete any and all research data that has been submitted to us through our Services. It is your responsibility at all times to ensure that you are in compliance with all applicable rules, policies, and regulations at the institutional, administrative, and federal levels regarding retention of research data, including, but not limited to, United States regulations governing retention and disposal of research records.**

_Right to Object_.  You have the right to object to the user of Personal Data for direct marketing uses, scientific uses, or historical research.  If you do not wish to have your Personal Data shared with third parties, contact our Data Protection Officer as described at the end of this document.  If you do not wish to receive future commercial messages from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the message you receive. (But note that you may continue to receive certain communications from us, such as transactional or relationship messages, and/or messages about your account/profile).

_Right to Restrict Processing_.  You have the right to request that we stop processing your Personal Data.

_Right to Data Portability_.  You have the right to request that we provide your Personal Data for the purpose of sharing it with another service provider (through a secure process).

_Filing a Complaint_. If you are not satisfied with how we manage your Personal Data, you have the right to make a complaint to a data protection regulator. A list of National Data Protection Authorities can be found here: [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm).

**8.               ****Retention**

We will retain Personal Data for the period necessary to fulfill the lawful purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

**9.               ****Access from Outside the United States**

If you are visiting the Services from outside the United States, please be aware that Personal and Non-Personal Data is transferred to, stored in, and processed in the United States. ****

**10.            ****Data Protection Officer**

Please see below for information regarding our appointed Data Protection Officer.

If you have an inquiry regarding your Personal Data, pursuant to the rights listed in the preceding section (above), please send your message to the following:

Parade

Attention:  Data Protection Officer for Parade.com

2451 Atrium Way

Nashville, TN 37214

USA

E-mail:  [dpo@amgparade.com](mailto:dpo@amgparade.com)

**11.            ****Links to third partysites**

Our Service(s) may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us.  If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site.  Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Athlon of those other websites, their content or services, or the persons or entities associated with those websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites.  We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.  We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of all third-party websites or services that you may visit. ****

**12.            ****Applicability of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

We do not sell products or services for purchase by anyone under the age of thirteen (13).  In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), we will never knowingly request or solicit Personal Data from anyone under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent.  In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such Personal Data without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.  We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors are not using the Service(s).

**13.            ****Your California privacy rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the Service(s) who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what Personal Data (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties.  Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. Under Section 1798.83, California residents are entitled to request and obtain such information, by e-mailing a request to [help@amgparade.com](mailto:help@amgparade.com).

**14.            ****Changes to the Privacy Policy**

As stated above, we will make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. It is our custom to provide notification on this page when we make material changes.  The date that this Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.  You are responsible for ensuring that you periodically visit our site(s) or Service(s) and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

**15.            ****Contact information**

If you have any questions or comments concerning this Privacy Policy, you may contact our representative(s) with the following information:

Waller Lansden Dortch & Davis, LLP

511 Union Street, Suite 2700

Nashville, TN  37219

USA

Attention:  Julian L. Bibb, Esq.

E-mail:  [julian.bibb@wallerlaw.com](mailto:julian.bibb@wallerlaw.com)
